Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Was it a dream?
هل كان حلما؟
Hey, let go.
مهلا، دعها تذهب.
Hey, what were you doing just now?
مهلا، ماذا كنت تفعل للتو؟
I was just saying hi to someone I've never seen before.
كنت فقط أقول مرحباً لشخص لم أره من قبل.
You misunderstood.
لقد أخطأت الفهم.
You say hi to people sleeping?
هل تقول مرحباً للأشخاص النائمين؟
Sometimes.
أحيانا.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
You're still up. Were you waiting for me?
مازلت مستيقظًا. هل كنت تنتظرني؟
No way.
مستحيل.
So sad.
حزين جداً.
Who is he? He's cute.
من هو؟ إنه لطيف.
Cute, my foot.
لطيف، قدمي.
What does going to university
ماذا يعني الذهاب إلى الجامعة؟
have anything to do with living with someone?
هل لها علاقة بالعيش مع شخص ما؟
I guess it's like a practice?
أعتقد أنها مثل التدريب؟
I really don't understand what Okhee is thinking.
أنا حقا لا أفهم ما يفكر فيه أوكي.
But she cares about you the most.
لكنها تهتم بك أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
Never mind, I'll just hold out for a month.
لا بأس، سأصمد لمدة شهر فقط.
So don't cause unnecessary trouble too.
لذلك لا تتسبب في حدوث مشاكل غير ضرورية أيضًا.
Well, that depends on how you fair.
حسنًا، هذا يعتمد على كيفية تعاملك.
Drink this.
اشرب هذا.
You always drink this when you're sick.
تشرب هذا دائمًا عندما تكون مريضًا.
How did you know I was sick?
كيف عرفت أني مريض؟
I heard it from Okhee.
سمعت ذلك من أوكي.
Why does she keep contacting you?
لماذا تستمر في الاتصال بك؟
Sorry for causing trouble.
عذرا على التسبب في المشاكل.
I like it though.
انا احب ذلك على الرغم من ذلك.
I went out because it was cloudy outside,
خرجت لأنه كان الجو غائما في الخارج،
but I couldn't even buy my book.
ولكنني لم أتمكن حتى من شراء كتابي.
This?
هذا؟
You...
أنت...
This is the first print version. Where did you get it?
هذه هي النسخة المطبوعة الأولى. من أين حصلت عليها؟
Give me a kiss.
أعطني قبلة.
Have you ever been slapped by a book?
هل سبق وأن صفعتك كتاب؟
He knows how to smile.
يعرف كيف يبتسم.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
My name is Han Dongha who just moved in today.
اسمي هان دونغها الذي انتقل للتو اليوم.
My name is Kang Seonjae.
اسمي كانج سيونجاي.
Seems like you were sleeping.
يبدو أنك كنت نائما.
Just a little.
فقط قليلا.
I was probably too tired so I got sleep paralysis.
ربما كنت متعبًا جدًا فأصبت بشلل النوم.
But Seonjae–I mean, Mr. Seonjae,
لكن سيونجاي - أعني السيد سيونجاي،
how should I address you?
كيف يمكنني أن أخاطبك؟
Well... You can just call me hyung.
حسنًا... يمكنك فقط مناداتي هيونغ.
Okay, Seonjae hyung.
حسنًا، سيونجاي هيونج.
But...
لكن...
Why?
لماذا؟
You're really handsome.
أنت وسيم حقا.
You have good taste.
لديك ذوق جيد.
Stop talking nonsense. Go to sleep.
توقف عن الكلام الفارغ. اذهب للنوم.
Why did you tell him that?
لماذا قلت له ذلك؟
He's so cute.
إنه لطيف للغاية.
Why? Are you jealous?
لماذا؟ هل انت غيور؟
I heard human blood is delicious,
سمعت أن الدم البشري لذيذ،
and we have one living with us now..
ولدينا واحد يعيش معنا الآن.
This is God's revelation.
هذا هو وحي الله.
Do you remember the Romanian phrase we learned?
هل تتذكر العبارة الرومانية التي تعلمناها؟
I almost forgot.
لقد نسيت تقريبا.
When you suck blood, you can't cause harm to humans
عندما تمتص الدم، لا يمكنك أن تسبب ضرراً للإنسان
or reveal your identity.
أو الكشف عن هويتك.
First, bite the vein.
أولاً، عض الوريد.
You should suck only an appropriate amount of blood.
ينبغي عليك امتصاص كمية مناسبة من الدم فقط.
If you suck too much, you might lose control.
إذا امتصصت كثيرًا، فقد تفقد السيطرة.
The conditions for whether a human is suitable for bloodsucking are
الشروط التي تحدد ما إذا كان الإنسان مناسبًا لمص الدم هي
height, weight, and pulse...
الطول والوزن والنبض
Why are there so many?
لماذا يوجد الكثير منهم؟
It's going to take forever to read this.
سوف يستغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلاً لقراءة هذا.
Shall we ask Seonjae when he comes?
هل نسأل سيونجاي عندما يأتي؟
Or we could just ask Joowon.
أو يمكننا فقط أن نسأل جووون.
We can't ask Joowon that!
لا يمكننا أن نطلب ذلك من جووون!
He...
هو...
[Resume: Han Dongha]
[السيرة الذاتية: هان دونغها]
This is quite remarkable.
وهذا أمر رائع للغاية.
My home is in the countryside, so I couldn't get it printed.
يقع منزلي في الريف، لذلك لم أتمكن من طباعته.
How much of a countryside is it?
ما مدى الريف الذي تعيش فيه؟
The kind surrounded by mountains.
النوع المحيط بالجبال.
You came to Seoul alone for school?
هل أتيت إلى سيول وحدك للمدرسة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Where do you live now?
أين تعيش الآن؟
I'm living in a share house nearby.
أنا أعيش في منزل مشترك قريب.
I see.
أرى.
But why did you decide to apply here?
ولكن لماذا قررت التقديم هنا؟
I liked sweets since I was a kid, so...
لقد أحببت الحلويات منذ أن كنت طفلاً، لذلك...
Okay.
تمام.
Then, when can you go to work?
إذن متى يمكنك الذهاب إلى العمل؟
That's the most important.
هذا هو الأهم.
Right now.
الآن.
[Ice Cube, Lee Joowon]
[آيس كيوب، لي جو وون]
This is for the umbrella.
هذا للمظلة.
No, that's not what I meant.
لا، هذا ليس ما قصدته.
Let's keep a distance between us.
دعونا نحافظ على مسافة بيننا.
[Lee Joowon]
[لي جو وون]
Why was Han Dongha's room suddenly changed?
لماذا تغيرت غرفة هان دونغها فجأة؟
Is Joowon spying on us
هل يتجسس علينا جووون؟
just in case we bite him?
فقط في حالة عضنا له؟
Is it because of me?
هل هذا بسببي؟
Did you bite him?
هل عضضته؟
I didn't get to taste it though.
ولكنني لم أتمكن من تذوقه.
Brother, let us have him.
أخي، دعنا نأخذه.
This is our first chance.
هذه فرصتنا الأولى.
But do we have to change rooms?
ولكن هل يجب علينا تغيير الغرف؟
Why can't he drink some blood since living under the same roof?
لماذا لا يستطيع شرب بعض الدماء طالما أنه يعيش تحت سقف واحد؟
He hates that.
انه يكره ذلك.
What does human blood taste like?
ما هو طعم الدم البشري؟
Is it good?
هل هو جيد؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Is it different from blood plasma?
هل هو مختلف عن بلازما الدم؟
Hey. They can't be compared.
مهلا، لا يمكن مقارنتهم.
You're so daring.
أنت جريئة جدًا.
What if you get caught?
ماذا لو تم القبض عليك؟
The moment the teeth bite through the flesh,
في اللحظة التي تعض فيها الأسنان اللحم،
the sweetness of human blood spread instantly.
انتشرت حلاوة الدم البشري على الفور.
The refreshing blood will flow down through the esophagus–
الدم المنعش سوف يتدفق إلى أسفل عبر المريء-
What flows along the esophagus?
ما الذي يتدفق على طول المريء؟
It's a gift to commemorate your first day at work.
إنها هدية للاحتفال بيومك الأول في العمل.
Go eat it with your housemates.
اذهب وتناوله مع زملائك في المنزل.
Okay.
تمام.
Even if it's just for a month, I should get along with them.
حتى لو كان ذلك لمدة شهر واحد فقط، يجب أن أتفق معهم.
I'm home.
أنا الوطن.
Huh? Why is my luggage outside?
هاه؟ لماذا أمتعتي بالخارج؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Can't you see? I'm moving your stuff.
ألا ترى؟ أنا أنقل أغراضك.
Who allowed you to do that?
من سمح لك بفعل ذلك؟
If you don't like me, just tell me.
إذا كنت لا تحبني فقط أخبرني.
Why do such a despicable thing?
لماذا تفعل مثل هذا الشيء الحقير؟
Huh?
هاه؟
You told me not to interfere with your private life,
لقد طلبت مني عدم التدخل في حياتك الخاصة،
but you're entering my room on your own accord?
لكنك تدخل غرفتي بمحض إرادتك؟
Are you the landlady?
هل أنت صاحبة المنزل؟
Everything's moved out.
لقد تم نقل كل شيء إلى الخارج.
Is there only one bag left?
هل تبقى كيس واحد فقط؟
You misunderstood.
لقد أخطأت الفهم.
I'll move out on my own in a month.
سأنتقل للعيش بمفردي خلال شهر.
So don't worry.
لذلك لا تقلق.
What's with the two of them?
ما الأمر مع الاثنين؟
It feels off.
إنه يشعر بالغرابة.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I shouldn't have done that.
لا ينبغي لي أن أفعل ذلك.
Dongha.
دونغها.
Your room was moved to the first floor.
لقد تم نقل غرفتك إلى الطابق الأول.
Didn't you see the text?
ألم ترى النص؟
Text?
نص؟
Yes.
نعم.
The room on the first floor is bigger and nicer.
الغرفة في الطابق الأول أكبر وأجمل.
I...
أنا...
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I thought you were ostracizing me,
اعتقدت أنك كنت تنبذني،
so I misunderstood you.
لذلك لقد أساءت فهمك.
I want to get along with you!
أريد أن أتعايش معك!
Though it's just a month,
على الرغم من أنه مجرد شهر،
we'd still be living under the same roof after all...
مازلنا نعيش تحت سقف واحد بعد كل شيء...
This is not your home.
هذا ليس منزلك.
He's at it again.
لقد فعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
He may sound cold,
قد يبدو باردًا،
but he changed your room for your sake.
لكنّه غيّر غرفتك من أجلك.
So don't think of it too much.
لذلك لا تفكر في هذا الأمر كثيرًا.
For my sake?
من أجلي؟
Joowon feels that you shouldn't stay by yourself on the second floor.
يعتقد جووون أنه لا ينبغي لك البقاء بمفردك في الطابق الثاني.
After you get to know us,
بعد أن تعرفت علينا،
you'd know that Joowon's the most humane among us.
ستعرف أن جو وون هو الأكثر إنسانية بيننا.
Humane? Him?
انساني؟ هو؟
Yes.
نعم.
You're probably saying that cause you're close to him.
ربما تقول هذا لأنك قريب منه.
Do we look close?
هل ننظر عن كثب؟
Yes.
نعم.
When I saw the two of you together last time,
عندما رأيتكما معًا في المرة الأخيرة،
you seemed close.
لقد بدوت قريبًا.
Anyway, don't fight and get along.
على أية حال، لا تقاتلوا وتوافقوا.
Got it, hyung.
فهمت، هيونغ.
He's good at cutting tomatoes.
إنه جيد في تقطيع الطماطم.
Did he learn it?
هل تعلمه؟
But... we can't eat this.
لكن... لا يمكننا أن نأكل هذا.
But this is his sincerity.
ولكن هذه هي صدقته.
Did you put something in it?
هل وضعت شيئا فيه؟
What?
ماذا؟
It's really delicious.
إنه لذيذ حقا.
Really?
حقًا؟
Well...
حسنًا...
I made some toast.
لقد صنعت بعض الخبز المحمص.
I'm full.
أنا ممتلئة.
Even his rejection's so casual.
حتى رفضه كان عرضيًا.
Done cleaning the bathroom.
تم الانتهاء من تنظيف الحمام.
When can I finish cleaning this place?
متى يمكنني الانتهاء من تنظيف هذا المكان؟
You don't look like someone who likes books.
أنت لا تبدو كشخص يحب الكتب.
Then what do I look like?
إذن كيف أبدو؟
Are you done looking?
هل انتهيت من البحث؟
When did I look...
متى نظرت...
I'm talking about the book.
انا اتحدث عن الكتاب.
Ah...
اه...
Right.
يمين.
Don't touch my stuff
لا تلمس أغراضي
in the future.
في المستقبل.
He's so annoying.
إنه مزعج للغاية.
This is amazing.
هذا مدهش.
I think my chronic rhinitis is healed.
أعتقد أن التهاب الأنف المزمن الذي أعاني منه قد تم شفاؤه.
Cold-blooded man.
رجل ذو دم بارد.
No, he's not even human.
لا، إنه ليس إنسانًا حتى.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Yes.
نعم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I don't know if I should say this now...
لا أعلم هل يجب علي أن أقول هذا الآن...
But what's your weight?
ولكن ما هو وزنك؟
It's over for us, right?
لقد انتهى الأمر بالنسبة لنا، أليس كذلك؟
According to the rules, his weight isn't the standard for blood sucking.
وفقا للقواعد، وزنه ليس هو المعيار لامتصاص الدم.
That's what I think, at least.
هذا ما أعتقده، على الأقل.
Lee Okhee!
لي أوكي!
I knew this would happen.
لقد علمت أن هذا سوف يحدث.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
That's what she meant by he can't be eaten.
هذا ما تعنيه عندما تقول أنه لا يمكن أكله.
I was looking forward to it...
لقد كنت أتطلع إلى ذلك...
Even when I was eating expired blood plasma,
حتى عندما كنت أتناول بلازما الدم منتهية الصلاحية،
I have been holding out with this thought.
لقد كنت متمسكًا بهذه الفكرة.
He's a prey that can't be eaten.
إنه فريسة لا يمكن أكلها.
Let's ask him to just move out, okay?
فلنطلب منه أن يخرج فقط، حسنًا؟
I think that's better.
أعتقد أن هذا أفضل.
Then let him gain weight.
ثم دعه يكتسب وزنا.
I like Han Dongha.
انا أحب هان دونغها.
So let him eat well and sleep well,
فليأكل جيدا ولينام جيدا،
and gain weight.
وزيادة الوزن.